All right, guys. For this fourth play, I need you guys to
evaluate some things that won't show up on the stat sheet.
Things like charisma,
character, and passion.
For the fourth play, we're going to dissect tone.
Can you say all of the correct words and still provide terrible customer service?
Absolutely. Watch this.
Welcome to Domino's. What can I get you?
Technically, that's correct, but let's try again.
Hey, welcome to Domino's. How are you doing today?
What can I get started for you?
Same basic message, completely different experience.
Team, it's not just what you say, it's how you say it.
Your tone matters, your facial expression matters,
your body language, your eye contact, all of it
matters.